So welcome ladies to our girlfriend experience call.
As I was just saying, I think this is going to be a really useful one,
especially for
newbies and people watching back because, as Georgia said, it's a fundamental
of webcam,
you know, if you can get the girlfriend experience, if you can hone your craft
in that then,
you know, you potentially earn in a lot of money, so hopefully we'll give some
insight
and go over a few tips and things today and you'll have something to go away
with.
So I hand over to you, Georgia, shall I have a fist, first little bear?
Yeah.
Nice.
So what is GFE?
GFE stands for Girlfriend Experience and it's a huge part of webcam.
If you nail GFE, you are on to a winner.
Most clients just want to be listened to and made to feel special and you can
deliver this
to them by giving them the girlfriend experience.
Get to know your client and act genuinely interested about them, interested to
learn
about them, sorry, remember or write down and pretend to remember things about
them.
Laugh at their jokes, find common ground between you both and let your client
know about all
the things you have in common.
Make them feel like you have a genuine connection and maybe you do and you don
't need to pretend.
So you get with girlfriend experience, I think with like most of, most on cam
usually, most
of the clients, all they want is just a connection and to feel heard and seen
because maybe
in their lives they don't feel that way and so this is where we come in and we
can like
really just give them a space to just be themselves, explore their kings,
fantasies, whatever
it is and just give them a safe space to just be able to explore themselves.
And if you remember things about them and stuff like that, then they're really
going
to love that and keep coming back.
I've had regulars that I've had for nine years and I know other girls that I've
known
like and you as well, like you've had regulars the whole time you've been on
cam like four
or five years.
So yeah, they definitely come back for sure and this is amazing because in slow
times
like if I log on and I've not been online for a while, I'm almost guaranteed a
regular
that I've had from like years ago, come into my chat room even if I'm not on
the front
page or stuff like that because I'm in this hot list from all those years ago
and for
the new girls, a hot list is basically where the clients save a certain amount
of girls
that they really like.
So when they go online, they don't have to browse through the hundreds of girls
online,
they just look at their hot list and then it'll pop up to say that you're
online and
then they'll come chat with you.
So yeah, so with the girlfriend experience, you really are building up regular
clients
because they fall in love basically and they really like full, but the fantasy
that you're
you're giving them and and yeah, they'll keep coming back and spending and this
is what
we want.
So we'll head to the next slide please, Elle.
How can we use GFE on webcam?
There are many ways to explore GFE on webcam and it should be rather easy to
think of things
to say to your clients as you just need to think about how you would interact
with your
partner and go from there.
Below are some ideas of how to use GFE on webcam.
Okay, so make your client feel seen, heard and appreciated.
So I already mentioned that one.
So yeah, you couldn't tell them how you like what he's wearing, you like his
hair, you
know, sit and features above his face or whatever else you can see and just
give him
some nice compliments and stuff like that.
Maybe he doesn't get them in life, you know, and it's nice that we can give
them to him
and then you can make him feel appreciated by saying, you know, thank you for
always
coming and chatting with me, I love our, I love our charts, like, you know, I
look forward
to it so much.
You're the only one that I enjoy chatting to on here, you know, stuff like that
, like
make them feel really special and you could be saying that to 10 guys, but it's
okay.
You know, and so remember things about your client.
So this is like super important to feel and you're not going to remember all
the things
about everyone, even if in the moment you feel like you are.
So we've said this before, but I suggest getting a no pads and just having a
next to
your laptop or computer or whatever.
And then when you're on a call with the client, you can jot down the username.
And then after the call, you can write down things that you remember about him.
He has a dog call marks, he's going away on the weekend.
He likes bananas or whatever, I don't know.
And then you can bring up the next time bananas and then you can bring up the
next time your
chart.
He's like, oh, how's Max doing?
You know, how was your weekend in Paris or whatever?
And he'll think, wow, this, this girl really likes me, she remembers, you know?
So yeah, that's a good thing to get with peak clients.
Okay, so you can plan come dates and ask your clients where they will take you
on a date
and remember it's all fantasy.
So you can say to your client, I've really enjoyed this session with you, can't
wait
to do it again.
Shall we plan a little date for next time, maybe Wednesday at 3pm or whatever
it is.
And then use it both like email and or text and call and back and forth,
excited for your
next session.
And obviously that's great because then they're coming back.
And you can always ask them and I like to do this because then you can talk
about it for
a long time.
And obviously as we know the longer we are in the chart, the more money that we
make,
you can say, where would you take me on a date?
And they can say, you know, I'll take you here and there and you can say, oh, I
'd wear
this like cute little black dress for you with some sexy underwear underneath
and maybe
we can do this and then we can do that and blah, blah, blah, blah and just talk
for
a long time and make a lot of money from that conversation.
So build a connection with your client.
And this is like super important because like I said, they just want to feel
like a connection
and feel seen and stuff like that.
So it works a lot better if you actually are into your client, like if you
actually like
them and figured it a nice pace.
And then obviously you don't need to be into them to the point where you want
to be with
them or anything like that.
I just mean it's nice if you get along with them.
And I think that it's a good practice for yourself to only really keep seeing
the clients
that you do have a good connection with or that you least get along with.
Because if you're logging on there and you know there's a client that you
really don't
like to have this session with an hour, whatever it's going to be and you dread
it and stuff
like that, maybe it's just not worth it, maybe it's good letting that client go
to make space
for the clients who you do have a good rapport with.
So yeah, I think that's quite important.
I think that's more for your sake as well because yeah, like I said, you don't
want to
be logging on dread and having to speak to certain clients.
And trust me, there are nice ones like the, I know some of the newer girls
maybe you're
not having spoke to many people yet.
So I really like my clients, like they're really nice and I'm grateful for all
of them
because they've been coming back for so long.
So yeah, there are nice guys on there.
And finally, understand your client's needs and deliver it to him.
So with the girlfriend experience, it's kind of just individual to each client
because
some clients like you to be at this way or sitting while or whatever else.
So in the beginning when you're first getting to know your clients, you'll
start to see
what he likes and what he doesn't like.
And then you can give them that version of your persona when you're in session
with him.
So head on to the next slide, please.
Oh, no, there's one more, maybe there's a few.
And phone calls and texts to keep you connected to your clients outside of
webcam.
So this is a really good one because when you're in between your sessions, you
can like,
you can call or you can text your client and that way you've still got that
connection
with them and they've not, you know, they've not forgot about yet or they've
not like went
on there and found somebody else and then or whatever else, at least you're
keeping the
like, keeping the communication open and you get paid for that as well for
phone calls
and texts.
So although it's not as much as on webcam, you still make money from it and
everything
adds up.
So in between your sessions, you just couldn't text and you know, I don't know,
can you send
picture messages, Lorna?
Can you do that?
I've just realised I don't know if you could do that.
I don't think it's possible, is it?
Now I was going to say maybe you can send picture messages, but maybe not, okay
.
But yeah, you maybe you can just say, oh, I'm wearing my new sexy underwear
today, like
come see me on camera and I can't wait to show you I bought it just for you,
all this
kind of stuff.
It's always just for them that they're super special ones that you do
everything for.
So yes, that's a good way to keep connected.
And that's literally what you just said.
I have like the same lines go round in my head all the time.
So dress up for your clients and I wore this just for you as you like me and
red.
So if they've said they like, you know, to see you when I sit in underwear set
or sit
in dress or whatever else, just put that on the next time and then be like, oh,
I wore
this, especially for you and yeah, just make them feel good.
Like the better you make them feel the more they want to come back, you know
what I mean?
Like on the with the girlfriend experience clients because that's what they
want.
They want to feel good.
And finally, make a private album just for your client of you.
You can say things like, I took some really naughty photos just for you.
So for the new girls, I know you can see you've got your free gallery and your
private gallery
where people have to pay to view those pictures.
You can make private albums, which can only be viewed by people that you give a
pin code
to.
So they put in it put in this pin code and then they still have to pay to view
it as well.
So then it's only for their eyes only, but you can give it a more than one
person.
So you can do this for a few crimes at once and the others are not going to
know that
the other people have viewed it.
So, yeah, that's another good way to just get some extra money out of your
regulars and
do something nice for them because they're going to love it.
You know, if they're seeing like naughty pictures of you at all, any pictures
of you.
So yeah, if they're a big spencer as well, like gauge on how much you're going
to cost
and how much you're going to price their album for, sorry, depending on how
much they spend.
If they're coming with you all the time and spending the money, then I would
make the price
high because, you know, that they could afford it.
But if they're not coming as much and maybe they haven't got as much money,
then I would
lower the price a little bit because I still want to make the sale, of course,
but, you
know, just depends on the clients I would charge more like a certain price.
So yes, they're just some things that you can do and come, we'll head to the
next slide.
Just on that as well, because I realised I don't think we've put it on here,
but when
you say about different prices for different clients for that private album, I
mean, that's
a good thing to mention in general, isn't it?
Like if I know I've got, because sometimes you'll have a regular and they
literally do
fall in love with you a little bit and they'll be coming back and talking to
you every day.
So you know, if you've got a couple of those, then I'll put my prices up, my
webcam prices
up a little bit because I know that they won't really notice and they'll come
back and see
me anyway.
So your prices you can put up and down depending on how many regulars you've
got.
If you've got loyal people, then it's good to put your prices up a bit.
Yes, definitely.
Yeah, like you said, they'll never know because they're not only coming with us
on there.
Even if they say they are just like we say that, "Oh, you're the only one that
I want
to talk to."
We say that to like 50 of them, they're probably coming with more girls and
they're not going
to know if the prices went up by like 0.5 credits, you know, and that goes a
long way
like if you don't know our conversation.
So yes.
I don't believe that.
I think they're only coming.
Oh, yes.
You live in your fantasy now.
No, I'm sorry.
Okay.
Okay, do you want to do this one or should I do it?
I don't know, so I'd rather do it.
Oh, go on.
Go on.
How's it?
Yeah.
Go on.
I'll take over next.
Okay.
So building your GFE persona, for your persona, this could be a little
different for each
clients already said that.
Think about your jobs, hobbies and sexual interests.
So let's say you've got a client and you know that he's into the whole
girlfriend's
experience.
And he's quite like, quite like a vanilla and stuff like that.
There may be like the way you went to wrap with them.
You should be a little bit that way, like you don't want to tell them that you
're super
wild and you're into all this crazy stuff if he's really not like that and not
into that,
you know.
So I would find out what they like and then I would tell them that basically I
'm into
the same things and stuff like that and I've got the same sexual interests and
whatever
else because, yeah, because I just, you just want them to feel like, user like,
you know,
user got a lot of common ground, like we said earlier and user like super
connected.
So, yeah, but I can't even get me where it's out.
Depends on each client depends on what type of person I am basically.
And it's always within my, like, what I feel comfortable with to, I'm not going
to act
a certain way for a certain client just because I know they like that or like,
if I didn't
like it, like if it made me feel uncomfortable or anything like that.
So always just stay within your boundaries and what makes you feel good as well
and update
your profile.
So new clients see that you offer GFA and make it more person, make it a more
personal
read so they feel like you're a real person to connect with.
So yeah, I think this one like, it really goes a long way and because if he's a
browser
with a website, you'll see that quite a lot of profiles are similar within the
way that
they set out.
There's a lot of like, I do this, this and this and I've got big boobs and like
, small
waist, big ass and this, this, this and like, you know, the right all of this,
like, they
describe what they look like and what they do on cam, rather than what they
actually
like and what they're into.
And I feel like your profile, it's going to attract, however, it's set out, it
's going
to attract certain clients.
So if you make it a little bit more personal and a little bit more like real
and genuine,
even if it's not, even if it's stuff that isn't about you, it's about your
persona, you're
going to connect with clients who are a little bit more into that rather than
the clients
who want the hardcore stuff.
So yes, so you can update your profile with this.
You can think about what to wear and where to come.
So you wrote this one, Rowan, I'm wondering what you mean about like, what
would you say
about where to come?
Yeah, I guess I was thinking about a regular that I've got, quite a recent one,
I've probably
had him for a couple months or so, and he loves it, because he obviously thinks
he's
the only one that I enjoy coming with.
And he thinks that he's the only one that I'll come in different places with.
So I literally wear a shirt or a work outfit and I'll be at the kitchen table
or something.
So in his eyes, it feels a bit more personal that he's getting a look into my
life that
other guys wouldn't.
So that's just one example, but yeah, I feel like moving around the house a bit
, or even
like you do sometimes like, you know, on a train or on the back of the car or
while you're
out and about, like it gives them a bit of a look into your life, doesn't it?
It makes it a bit more like, oh, you're seeing this, but no one else does, you
know?
Yeah, totally.
Yeah.
Okay, got you.
FYI, they love that, by the way, if you're in a car, ever, girls, and you're
obviously
not driving it, if you're in the passenger or in the back seat or whatever, put
your cam
on.
If you can, if you're with somebody, obviously that, you know, you feel
comfortable to have
it on with.
So I was going on super long journeys last year, like 10 hour journeys in a car
.
And my partner was driving.
So I was in the back on cam and I've never been busier, like, as you know, like
as like
new girls, especially as well, people that are coming in, a lot, like most
people will
leave straight away, they just like to browse through all the girls online and
that's totally
normal.
Don't worry about that.
But when I was in the back of the car, most people wasn't leaving.
They were like fighting over the stay and put me in private.
I was like, what?
It was amazing.
I was like, I just wanted to show, first of all, drive me round every time I
was on cam
because I was like, I've not been busier.
So although that's completely a different from girlfriend experience, while we
're on
the subject of it, and if you're ever in a car and you can come do it because
you'll
be very busy, because they like the whole risk of, oh, maybe someone can see
you and
blah, blah, blah.
So yeah, little tip there.
Okay.
And finally, take inspiration online from TV shows or elsewhere to tell stories
about
your persona.
So yes, that's that one done.
Thank you, Elle.
So we talked a little bit about giving your clients what they want.
So I thought that it might be helpful to break that down a bit more, especially
for
newbies or people that aren't used to the girlfriend experience.
So put together some questions to help you understand each unique client's
needs and
hopefully to keep them hooked.
So when slash why do they can?
So there's lots of different reasons why guys can, you know, your GFE, your
girlfriend
experience clients are so different, they're all so unique.
So we can't just be a certain person, like George said earlier, and expect that
to suit
everybody and everybody's coming with their own unique needs.
So knowing this, getting, you know, understanding and gauging why and when they
can can give
you a really good idea of what it is that they're coming for.
So maybe they're coming for company when they're away on business.
I've had lots of regulars like this and they just like to chat.
Literally we just talk about like politics or biscuits or like any old stuff
and they're
great clients and you know that they're just doing it for company because they
're away
and that's where they are and stuff like that.
Some clients maybe after the wives in bed, they're downstairs like secretly so,
you know,
maybe they're horny and that's and they want someone to connect with in that
way or maybe
they're feeling like disconnected and undesirable and so you making them feel
sexy and making
them feel wanted is going to get them coming back again and again.
Maybe they come back like astronaut out or actually they've been in a pub and
they want
to talk about their fantasies and so it's just a safe place for them to explore
what
their fantasies are with somebody.
So yeah, there's lots of different reasons and as you get to know them, you can
gauge
what it is they want when they come to you because it's not the same for
everybody.
What do they comment on or ask you about?
So it's really important to, I think especially when you're quite new on cam,
you can be a
lot of girls get caught in the trap of just trying too hard, like really trying
to see
the right things straight away, trying to be sexy straight away, you know,
trying to
get in there first with the sexy things so they don't leave your room but
actually,
you know, it's much better to just take a breath, relax into it a bit, you know
, smile
and look inviting and you know, like you're going to connect with them and you
're interested
in them and give them space to talk, you know, ask them questions but stay
curious about what
they're saying and you can notice so do they ask about your work or
achievements or your
love life like some people like to know about dating and, you know, it excites
them to hear
about whether you've been dating and stuff.
Do they ask about fantasies or experiences and if so, yeah, you know, maybe in
the interim
before next time we can, you can go on our website and look at the fantasy
writing call.
So there are different things that you can do depending on what they comment on
, what
they ask you about.
So yeah, tuning into their questions helps you understand their unique needs
rather than
a one-size-fits-all approach.
How can you expand on what they're telling you?
So if they allude to a fantasy or an interest, ask them about it.
You know, many guys, you know, this is a particular part of like the girlfriend
experience that
I love is when they come and just say like they might hint that, you know, they
've had
a certain experience and that they fancied someone like their teacher or
something when
they were younger and there's just a little snippet of it and if you can really
be curious
about it and act like you're a bit excited, you know, and curious, then it can
help them
to just open up and then they feel, you know, safe to explore that with you and
they might
want to come back again and again.
I mean, literally some guys come back and tell the same fantasy, don't they,
again and
again and again, literally for years, which is great because it's just like the
easiest
call ever, so let them tell you what they want to tell you, be curious and try
and expand
on what they're telling you.
It's okay if you don't understand something, you know, a particular kink or
something that
they're talking about, just ask them about it and they love to explain it to
you as long
as you're open and non-judgmental.
This is their tone, their body language or the words they use, so whether you
're doing
cam to cam, so maybe you can see them, the newbies, that's when you can see
their camera
as well as they can see you, or if you're just typing and you can't see them,
you can
notice how they come across, so, you know, you get to know pretty quickly, you
can sense
whether they're really confident or whether they're really shy and nervous, so
knowing
how they feel can help you to make them feel welcome.
So confident guys may want to be more playful, so you can be more playful, take
the piss even
a little bit, you know, and just have a bit of banter with them, or shy and
self-conscious
guys might benefit from gentle questioning and reassurance and just getting to
know you
and trust you a bit more.
And how often are they online, so knowing their login habits can help you to
build a
picture when you're likely to catch them and what they like from you, so, you
know, for
instance, I know I have certain regulars that I know will be there at certain
time,
so if I log in at like 1 o'clock on a Tuesday, I know there'll be a couple of
guys who are
in the office and who can from work and I know that they'll be there at that
time, and I
know kind of what they like because, you know, I've come to them for a long
time, so getting
to know when they're going to be about, it just makes them, makes it easier for
them
to come to you if you turn up when they're around, so, yeah, being available
when it's
convenient to them can help you build a relationship and keep them coming back.
So finally, stay safe and be yourself.
So remember that girlfriend-experienced clients can be diverse and can want
different things
and you don't have to please them all, like Georgia said earlier, you know, we
can't please
everybody and sometimes you know, it's not worth spending bad energy on
somebody and really
trying to draw it out and make it work because, you know, that space could be
taken up by
someone you enjoy being with, so the aim here is to get a few regulars who will
go out
of their way to spend virtual time with you and will have long money-making
conversations.
So it's better to be someone's glass of champagne than everyone's cup of tea.
Place your strengths and show your unique personality or have fun developing a
character
whatever makes you feel playful and confident and I think those of us that have
been doing
it a long time, we do both of these.
I mean, you can switch and change if one day you feel like showing up as
yourself and another
day you want to be a bit playful and do some acting, you know, that's fine, isn
't it?
You can mix it up.
Finally, it can be fun, rewarding and you can build real friendships with
clients during
GFE, but always be careful not to share too many personal details that you can
feel safe
and uphold your boundaries while you're working online.
And I think that's it from us.
So I thought that it would be nice if anybody wanted to either ask a question
or share a
little story or something about their experience with a girlfriend-experienced
client.
If anybody's got anything that they'd like to share or even something that we
haven't
mentioned, maybe if you've got a tip or a question or anything, is anybody, or
anything
they'd like to add?
I'm trying to see who's here.
Hi, Elona.
Yeah, I've got a little 77-year-old who is my little regular now and he emails
me every
night and every morning.
Oh, I just described what he's on his own, described cooking a meal for him and
doing
all little things and it's really so sweet and he tells me every night how I'm
precious
to him, me and the will to him and all that.
But you know, he does spend a lot on the calls.
He calls me over the day and I'm talking about, you know, the phones, it's a
good 15-20 minutes,
isn't it?
You know, it's good that.
Well, I've got another one who's a bit wilder who's now starting texting me all
day and
we've got a common link with football and stuff.
So like you say, it's just getting into finding the different interests, isn't
it?
You know, and things.
So you've got a little group of regulars now, it's quite good.
You get into finding out all just honing on something that they might, you
might have
in common or knowledge of, you know.
So I think it's going quite well for me at the moment.
Yeah, you're very great and how sweet, I love that, that book.
It's really nice because you find out what I sort of tuning in to what they
miss.
Like he's missing sort of like, you can tell he's lonely and I just hope we
could go for
a big, he lives in Brighton, walk along the sea, hold in hands.
Oh, when he loves it, you know.
The other one's a bit more sort of highly active, you know, a bit naughty in
that, but it's
all just good fun.
But like you say, I've picked up on most of the things that you have said and
it is work
and then now I was off a little bit because I wasn't, wasn't too well.
We went on a holiday, wasn't it, and I was a bit poorly before and I noticed I
've been
popping up a lot.
Must be in the hot list like you were saying.
I've got like five or six of them at the last couple of days, I've been quite
busy, you
know.
So it does work.
It really does.
Yes.
Makes sense.
I'm so happy to hear that honestly, it makes my heart feel like you're doing
well.
They're all different, they're all different personas, you know, each one of
the world
different age ranges and things and I've now got into like the little bit of a
character
for each one.
And at the end of it, they always say, "Oh, yours call me Mel, like, you know,
Melody.
Oh, Mel, I just know I can do anything and we have a chat and it's our safe
little play."
You know, it's, you know, I really enjoy, you know.
Oh, maybe so much for sharing.
I love it, Lauren.
And I love it when you voice-natant me and tell them me and yours.
Oh, yeah.
And I think that's a good point as well.
I mean, something that we haven't put in this PowerPoint is that, you know, as
much as we're
trying to make money here, we are providing something which is really valuable.
Like, you know, especially this old guy that lives old guy, he's all there and
he's great,
you know, but he's just very, very lonely as well.
And to think that somebody is going the extra mile just to send him, I'll just
send like
a little message, you know, and say, "Oh, hi, I hope you had a good day in that
."
So a little message now and again, and then it turns into the text, as old as
you know,
you can text me if you can't always talk, you know, and then the guy who texts
me just
message me now how blah, blah, blah, I enjoyed our chat today.
We're all these texts.
I mean, Craig, you must have sent me about 40, 50 texts.
You know, but it all ends up, doesn't it?
You know.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
And what a beautiful thing that you're doing for, you know, you know, you know,
it's just
just, I mean, it's a huge cause of illness and even death, isn't it?
Well, you know, this other guy, the older one, he sounded quite lonely, someone
's sort
of honed in and you could tell he was missing things and he was telling me
about his life
and all that.
So the other night, we had like a sort of supposed romantic dinner and we had
to dance
and we had a bit of a sexy ending like, "Well, you know, he absolutely loves it
."
And he always sleeps while I have to speak and to me.
I bet he's done with it.
Yeah.
So nice.
Oh, that's so good.
I just need to get on camera and try and get sourced, don't I?
He's doing so well, there's no, there's no groceries there, there's no pressure
.
Well, it's an apprenticeship for me, isn't it?
You know.
Yeah.
And you can have, you've got loads of loyal customers anyway.
So, yeah, that's so nice to hear and I love hearing about people's clients.
Yeah, I think you just, you just, I've tried different types of things,
different people
and then you suddenly get a change in the mask, you get to know you a bit and
you can
sort of hone in a bit then and then these two in particular realise that they
want more
of a bit of a personal thing that they're missing like you were saying before
and it's
really working actually because I'm getting more calls off them all the time
and that
you know, more chat.
So, yeah, it is good, you know.
Yeah.
And I think that's what's missing from, you know, lots of agencies and webcam
places
is that you don't, you don't get the training about how to connect with clients
.
You know, next, it's just like a sexual thing, that's the more you connect, the
longer, the
more time they want to spend with you and the nicer it is as well, it just
feels nice
doesn't it?
Oh, you're telling me the other day, 15 minutes on the phone about how he's
organising his
Google Drive, you know.
Great, you know.
Tell me more.
Oh dear.
Oh, thank you, Donna.
You're welcome.
Give yourself.
Does anybody else, does anyone else want to share something or ask a question?
Well, we're here.
I mean, it doesn't even have to be GFE related if you're a newbie and you've
got a question
that you want to ask while you've got our attention.
No.
We can write it in the chat if you want to.
Oh, just a quickie, I was just going to ask because I think a few people might
want to
ask as well.
I still need to get to upload some like no voice, like short voice messages and
things
because I think that'd be quite good.
I noticed when I was waiting, people said, "Oh, I'd like to hear your voice."
So I'd like to try and progress and get a few things uploaded, you know.
I don't know how long, perhaps just obviously only in a couple of minutes, isn
't it, the
most I suppose, you know, and just sort of try and replicate what they get on a
call
really.
I just thought that might be quite a good idea for me to do, you know?
Yeah, I think that's a great idea.
Yeah, I remember now you saying in the group, I think, Sam is going to say, "I
'll see if
I can look into it as well because I've got to use to upload it."
I mean, I've got a few things because I mean, there's a couple of things that
you tend to
say at the same time, but you need to just like make a nice little friend
anymore.
But a few people said, "Oh, you're away from me, you can miss," you know, sort
of thing.
I thought, "Oh, there's a bit of money opportunity here."
And I asked the couple and said, "Would you listen to it?"
And he said, "Oh, yeah, definitely do that."
So I think it's a good thing because obviously it keeps the money coming in,
doesn't it,
you know?
Well, passive income, isn't it, if it's already?
Yeah.
A little J.O. Iron on record for them.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Okay.
We'll give you a message.
Yeah.
And that's it.
That's it then.
It's set for today.
It was nice to see some new faces with some new names at least.
And yeah, we'll keep you posted about when the next call's going to be.
Well, the next call is actually next week at the same time, and it's going to
be the
welcome call.
So for all the new girls, I know there's two here today, but yeah, for all the
new girls,
it's very important to come along to this call because we'll just go through
all of
the stuff that all the newbies need to know.
So yeah, it's the same time next week on Monday, 9pm UK time.
And we actually have another call that we've just booked in, but the poster
hasn't been
done yet.
We'll see you in the next day or so.
So I'll let you know when it is, um, I'm going to sorry, one second.
It's a call on financial advice.
So, um, yeah, just all about like, you know, how you do your tax and the fact
that we registered
self-employed and stuff like that.
So it's really beneficial and this call and it's going to be in June.
It's going to be on Monday the 5th of, 5th of June at 9pm UK time.
So I think it's the Monday after the next one.
So yeah, in two weeks time.
So yeah, next Monday at 9pm on the Monday after will be the next two calls.
So yes, thank you for coming along, Gailies.
I hope you've learned something today.
And let us know, you're welcome to, yeah, thank you for sharing your stories as
well.
But yeah, let us know how you get on with the GFE stuff and how it works for
you and
your upcoming, upcoming calls.
Um, well, yeah, thank you very much, Gailies, and we'll see you soon.
Thank you.
Bye.
Ready.